

BATUHAN ENES BAŞAY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER STUDENT

CONTACT

P: +90 545 528 1997

E: <u>basaybatuhan@gmail.com</u>
W: <u>www.batuhanbasay.com</u>

A: Duzce, Turkey

SOCIAL



@batuhanbasay



batuhan-basay



@batuhan.basay

SKILLS

Programming Languages:

ASP.NET, Python, C#, C++, PHP

Web Desing:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js

Database:

MySql, MsSql, Microsoft Access

Operating Systems:

Ubuntu, Windows, Android

Design:

Photoshop, Canva, Pro Premier, XD

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Google Solution Challenge 2020 /

Team I&Others / 11th

- Teknofest 2020 /

Team MEKATEK Robotaxi / 12th

- Efor All Entrepreneurship Competition / Team Pole Star / 1.st

REFERENCE

<u>Merve İşler - Developer Relations Coordinator</u> <u>@Google</u>

PERSONAL SKILLS

Leadership, Project manager, Organized, Programmer, Team player, Fast learner

ABOUT

I plan to make a career in these fields by developing myself in the field of web programming and artificial intelligence programming. I see deep learning and fronted-backend software as the most suitable areas for me. I led the Google Developer Student Clubs Düzce University (GDSC Düzce) for 1 year. I am currently mentoring Tensorflow and Cloud at GDSC Turkey. I have developed projects in many hackathons so far. I developed a project in the autonomous vehicle category at Teknofest. My goal is to move forward with a company that follows technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TensorFlow & Cloud Mentor Google Developer Student Clubs Turkey

Sept 2021 - NOW Istanbul, Turkey (Working remotely)

Growrth & Strategy Lead AugeLab R&D Tech. Inc.

May 2021 - Oct 2021 Gebze, Turkey (Working remotely)

Lead Google Developer Student Clubs Duzce University

Sept 2020 - Sept 2021 Duzce University, Turkey

Software Intern Tepebasi Municipality

July 2017 - Aug 2017 Eskisehir, Turkey

Software Intern Eskisehir Metropolitan Municipality

June 2016 - July 2016 Eskisehir, Turkey

Junior Developer LondonMarketing

Sept 2015 - March 2016 London, England (Working remotely)

EDUCATION

Undergraduate Anadolu University

2019 - NOW Management Information Systems

Undergraduate Duzce University

2018 - NOW Computer Engineering

High School Sabiha Gokcen Vocational and Technical Anatolian

2014 - 2018 High School

Information Technologies - Software

CERTIFICATIONS

Nov 2020 EFOR All Entrepreneurship Competition -

Cerificate of Achievement

Google Developer Student Clubs

Google Developer Student Clubs

Aug 2021 Google DSC Leader Certification

Google Developer Student Clubs

Nov 2020 Google Developers ML DAYS Hackathon | Mentor

Google ML Days

Sept 2020 Teknofest 2020 - Robotaxi - Autonomous Vehicle

Competition

Turkey Team Foundation Technology

July 2020 2020 Solution Challange Perticipant | Team I&Others

Google Developers

May 2020 Google Solution Marathon 2020

Developer Student Clubs, Google Turkey

Note: You can check my linkedin account for my other certificates.